Next Preview
Picking Kanto Idol
next preview
Kotoba
Kotoba.
So that's what it means.
Yes, I am. As I mentioned earlier, I also write tanka poems,
Also, I usually like to write,
I write a blog, and I was asked to write tanka poems after reading my blog,
So there was that kind of connection,
I was informed that Mr. Yoshida had also mentioned it,
So it is a choice of words.
It is very important to me,
Do you take a lot of time to write something that will remain in your mind for a long time?
But you usually write down what comes to your mind.
Is that right?
So sometimes I make something out of something I've been thinking about for a long time, and other times it just comes to me at that moment,
Sometimes it takes a long time, and sometimes it is done quickly.
Sometimes it takes a lot of time, sometimes it's quick. Is this a notebook?
I've been doing that since I was very young,
When I was little, it was paper,
Paper? A notebook?
No, it's paper. Paper.
It was notebooks, but now I have a smartphone for quick access.
Oh, that.
Yes, that's right.
I've been doing it for a long time.
How old were you when you started doing that?
From nursery school.
From nursery school?
That's right.
I was interested in writing poems on manuscript paper and giving them to my mother when I was in nursery school,
Do you still have any of those things that you wrote down?
Yes, I do.
I'm currently doing my own Instagram page,
I write poems on it.
I wrote a poem to my mother when I was in nursery school,
If you give them to your mother, does she keep them?
Yes, she has it.
No, seriously?
Do all your fans know about that?
I don't know.
Oh, really?
So you're not even going to show it to them?
No, I don't.
It's embarrassing.
I see.
Did you ever think about writing something that would be born from now on, and putting it out there?
Right now, I really want to write lyrics,
Wow.
I've always wanted to do it,
Why do you have a craftsman for this?
No, that's too much of a spoiler.
Just say it. I'm going to put it out here.
You're putting it out here?
We're putting it out here?
Here?
It's okay. That's why.
I'm sorry. You're putting it out somewhere else?
I'm working on it.
You're doing it now?
I've been wanting to do it for a long time. I've been saying I wanted to do it for a long time,
I've been waiting and waiting and waiting.
I see.
But now I'm finally getting around to it.
As Tohoku-san's song.
A song by Tohoku-san.
Aren't you excited?
I've wanted to do it for a long time.
I see.
That's why you're the captain,
I don't know,
When I told him about the GPT chat,
I said, "Why don't you write a poem for the chat GPT? I said, "Why don't you write a poem for the chat GPT?
No, that's not it,
I don't have anything to do with it. He looked at me like, "No, it doesn't matter anymore,
I was more interested in it,
So there was your poem.
You have poems, after all.
You cherish words, and maybe someday we will get to hear a poem you write.Maybe someday we will hear a poem made by Mizuki, who cares about words.
Cute.
Next time preview
Or maybe it's fantasy-ish.
Or buying something.
something.
This show is
Yasuuke-san
Aotan
Kento-san
Mr. Haruusa
Gachikoi Taro
Thank you very much!
Ms. Lovelyn